You know,
when you believe you have incredible potential to make a move?
But reality puts you in something else.
Well,
that's me living a day without expectations,
but today I'm going to make some changes.
I thought about dressing in a tent,
but honestly.
Dude,
look at the price of that,
uncle.
Baby,
I couldn't ask for another
no,
I couldn't ask for
no.
I don't know if you know,
but I live inside a Chevette.
Just the price of the gas stove.
Forget it, man.
If I'm going to invest in something,
I need something ready.
I'm thinking about getting some Cacau Show truffles to resell.
You know,
I got like truffles.
Тих
fraction of what's coming,
i couldn't Ask for another.